question_data = [
    {
        "question": "Is TypeScript a statically-typed language?",
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Does Python support tail recursion?",
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is a trie data structure typically used for searching?",
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Does JavaScript support template metaprogramming?",
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is threading supported in C++?",
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Are tuples mutable in Python?",
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Does a transactional database guarantee data consistency?",
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is Rust's type system based on type inference?",
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Does Go support type aliases?",
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is a tree data structure typically used for sorting?",
        "answer": "False"
    }
]
